https://www.nightienight.co.uk/privacy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of
our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your
personal information.
(1)
What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a)
information about your computer and about your visits to and use of
this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser
type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;
(b)
information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us
on or in relation to this website, including information relating to
any purchases you make of our goods or services;
(c) information
that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us
(including name, address, telephone numbers, email address;
(d)
information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to
our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
(e)
any other information that you choose to send to us;
(2)
Cookies
We
use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web
server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is
then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from
the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web
browser.
We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your
browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we
obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to
improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also
use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our
website, and to personalise our website for you. Our advertisers may
also send you cookies.
Most browsers allow you to refuse to
accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all
cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and
selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will,
however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites,
including this one.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use
of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other
information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on
users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is
used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store
this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html .
(3)
Using your personal data
Personal
data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified
in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)
administer the website;
(b)
improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(c)
enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d)
send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(e)
send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f)
send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g)
send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(h)
send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications (relating
to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties
which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have
specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can
inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications
to be sent by emailing us at support@nightienight.co.uk ) ;
(i)
provide third parties with statistical information about our users –
but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
(j)
deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
We
will not without your express consent provide your personal information
to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
(4)
Other disclosures
In
addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes
identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose
information about you:
(a)
to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)
in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)
in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including
providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention
and reducing credit risk); and
(d)
to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5)
International data transfers
Information
that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between
any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use
the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
If you
are in the European Union, information which you provide may be
transferred to countries (including the United States and Japan) which
do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the
European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.
(6)
Security of your personal data
We
will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to
prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We
will store all the personal information you provide on our secure
servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us
will be encrypted using SSL technology.
Of course, data
transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot
guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.
(7)
Policy amendments
We
may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new
version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to
ensure you are happy with any changes.
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(8)
Your rights
You
may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold
about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment
of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email (to support@nightienight.co.uk ) at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in
advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we
will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your
personal data for marketing purposes.)
(9)
Third party websites
The
website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for
the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(10)
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(11)
Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to contact@nightienight.co.uk or by post to Nightie Night, Suite 163, 30 Red Lion Street, Richmond Upon Thames, Surrey. TW9 1RB
This privacy policy is based on a template
created and distributed by www.website-law.co.uk
